NICOLE ZELINGHER

FULL STACK
WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

914-255-4000

NICOLE.ZELINGHER@GMAIL.COM

WWW.NICOLEZ.COM

WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/NZELINGHER

WWW.GITHUB.COM/NIKKLZ

PROFILE

I am a passionate, energetic, and hard working sales professional and technophile turned web developer. My combination of 4+ years on the business side of tech and my lifelong interest in technology motivate me to stay current with the latest trends in development, while my creativity and drive inspire me to bring great ideas to life.

EXPERIENCE

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE | JAN 2018 - APR 2018

- Established a solid foundation in full stack development through completion of General Assembly's immersive 12 week program, logging 1000+ hours of coding time
- Designed and developed a variety of web applications using the latest technologies and best practices
- Partnered with other developers on group projects, mastering project workflow using GitHub
- Developed ability to teach myself a new language and framework, learning Elixir and Phoenix as an independent project

MAKERBOT

ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE | MAR 2015 - JAN 2017

- Drove organizational revenue by demonstrating strong sales techniques, regularly exceeding 100% of sales quotas
- Regularly interfaced with development and product teams to flesh out client business requirements
- Demonstrated a consistent ability to think creatively to establish new, unique prospecting methods
- Cultivated excellent, lasting relationships with prospects and clients

NKLZ

BIZ DEV & STRATEGY CONSULTANT | SEPT 2013 - PRESENT

- Collaborated with clients to create cohesive marketing plans, including tailored campaigns and strategies
- Developed clients brands and images to reflect core message and reach desired audience
- Crafted short and long term campaign goals, including the creation of measurables to track and maximize success

EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE

APRIL 2018

BACHELOR OF ARTS, COMMUNICATION

UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHSETTS AMHERST

MAY 2011

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- Node
- HTML5/CSS
- GitHub
- jQuery
- PostgreSQL

- MongoDB
- React
- Ruby On Rails
- Sinatra
- Elixir/Phoenix
- SASS